<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Conference on Prakhar Gupta</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/tags/conference/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Conference on Prakhar Gupta</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/tags/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Midwest Security Workshop 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/msw24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 20:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/msw24/</guid>
      <description>I had the opportunity of visiting the 9th midwestern security workshop hosted at purdue this year.&#xA;I found out about this through a grad student (Patrick) who used to be (and still kinda is?) a part of ECE 391 (Operating-Systems) Course Staff. I handn&amp;rsquo;t visited the purdue campus, and figured that this might be worth going to - even if i know nothing about computer security.&#xA;Well, nothing in the &amp;ldquo;formal&amp;rdquo; academic context.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Neuroscience 2024</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/sfn24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 19:12:24 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/sfn24/</guid>
      <description>The weekend Before I don&amp;rsquo;t know where to start for this blog entry. Things have been super hectic and it&amp;rsquo;s been a long time since I have written actual words/sentences that aren&amp;rsquo;t meeting notes or homework/lab reports. Well I guess this blog post will evolve into meeting notes once I get to the actual conference.&#xA;Neuroscience 2024, is conveniently happening in Chicago, from 10/5 (i think) to 10/9. I am going to be there on 10/7 and 10/8.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Supermicrosummit24</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/supermicrosummit24/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:55:40 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/supermicrosummit24/</guid>
      <description>Super Micro Open Stroage Summit 2024 https://www.thecube.net/events/supermicro/open-storage-summit-2024&#xA;I attended the last 2 events at this stummit. Here are my thoughts and notes:&#xA;The New High Performance Computing: Optimized Storage from HPC to AI Speakers:&#xA;Randy Kreiser Supermicro CJ Newburn NVIDIA Balaji Venkateshwaran DDN Bill Panos Solidigm CJ- The moderator looks like he is being held at gunpoint.&#xA;Rate at which usage models are changing&#xA;need for new infrastructure&#xA;new models characterized by large scale and making memory accesses of fine granularity</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
