<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ScreamingPigeon</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>I like computers...</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

    
    <item>
      <title>Flush Reload</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/flush_reload/</link>
      <description>
          Intro Last November, I got the chance to meet Daniel Genkin - at the Midwest Security Workshop. He is one of the authors/discoveres of SPECTRE and MELTDOWN , some of the most critical vulnerabilities discovered in the last decade. These were also unpatchable due to them being hardware vulnerabilities.
Bumping into Daniel was a happy coincidence for me. I was aware that MSW had a section on HW Security (which is why I went in the first place) - but I never knew that such an epic security researcher was going to be there.
          
          
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/blog">blog</a> <a href="/tags/computer-architecture">computer-architecture</a> <a href="/tags/security">security</a> </p>
          
          <p>Word Count: 2055</p>
          <p>Reading Time: 10 minutes</p>
          
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 15:09:05 CDT</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/flush_reload/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing an Out-Of-Order RISC-V CPU: part one</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/ooo_pt1/</link>
      <description>
          This post is about 5 months late. I created the markdown file on 12/23/2025 but never got around to writing anything to it. Now, I have some time on my hands (and I feel bad about not writing as often as I had planned to) - so I figured I will give this a shot again.
Last fall, I took ECE 411 the infamous computer-architecture class at my university. This was a class I was really looking forward to.
          
          
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/projects">projects</a> <a href="/tags/computer-architecture">computer-architecture</a> </p>
          
          <p>Word Count: 3124</p>
          <p>Reading Time: 15 minutes</p>
          
      </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 17:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/ooo_pt1/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermicrosummit24</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/supermicrosummit24/</link>
      <description>
          Super Micro Open Stroage Summit 2024 https://www.thecube.net/events/supermicro/open-storage-summit-2024
I attended the last 2 events at this stummit. Here are my thoughts and notes:
The New High Performance Computing: Optimized Storage from HPC to AI Speakers:
Randy Kreiser Supermicro CJ Newburn NVIDIA Balaji Venkateshwaran DDN Bill Panos Solidigm CJ- The moderator looks like he is being held at gunpoint.
Rate at which usage models are changing
need for new infrastructure
new models characterized by large scale and making memory accesses of fine granularity
          
          
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/blog">blog</a> <a href="/tags/conference">conference</a> </p>
          
          <p>Word Count: 529</p>
          <p>Reading Time: 3 minutes</p>
          
      </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 11:55:40 CDT</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/supermicrosummit24/</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making a POSIX (-ish?) Linux Kernel</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/ece391/</link>
      <description>
          Interactive Demo here Features include Concurrency through RoundRobin Scheduler Interrupt Support, Keyboard IO, RTC Custom read-only filesystem with POXIS(-ish?) syscalls x86_32 Paging exec() and exit() functionality for certain programs For academic integrity reasons, I cannot share the source code
This project also has mouse support, soundblasters, and real-time UART pvp TicTacToe implemented for extra credit. Not available in the online demo. This placed 3rd in the Design competition in SP24 
          
          
            <p>Tags: <a href="/tags/projects">projects</a> <a href="/tags/operating-systems">operating-systems</a> </p>
          
          <p>Word Count: 70</p>
          <p>Reading Time: 1 minutes</p>
          
      </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 03:39:15 &#43;0530</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/ece391/</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

